Finding Aid for the Mark Weber Jazz Collection, 1970-2005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photographs, Series 3.
  - Musical Groups, Subseries 4.; 76 photographs
    - Michael Vlatkovitch Trio, 1999 November 1; B&W snapshots (Box 15, Folder 6)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Vlatkovitch, Michael and Series 3: Subseries 4, Michael Vlatkovitch Quartet.
    - New Orleans, Louisiana (N.O.L.A.), 1982 June 26 - July 11; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Steve Masakowski, Mason Ruffner,Ellis Marsalis, Tyler's Beer Garden James Black Quinitet
    - Noah Young Quartet, 1982 April 16; B&W 8x10 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      Taken at the Claremont Colleges, Ca. Also pictured; David Angel, Richard Davis, Fred Stofflet and Noah Young.
    - Out of Context, 2001-2004, inclusive; B&W and color snapshots (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Taken at Outpost in Albuquerque, New Mexico, rehearsal at Carla Barlow's. Also pictured; Carla Barlow, Stefan Dill, Steve Feld, Katie Harlow, and Jefferson Voorhees.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Deane, J.A.; Dill, Stefan
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra, undated; B&W 11x14 and 8x10 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
      In 1970, the band was billed as the Community Cultural Orchestra and in August became the Community Cultural Arkestra. By the summer of 1971 .. they .. adopted the name the Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (PAPA).Isoardi, S.L. The dark tree, c2006, p.113. See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Tapscott, Horace. See also Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - Paraphrase Trio, 2001 April 14; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Tim Berne, Drew Gress, and Tom Rainey.
    - Pee Wee Crayton & His Ultimates of Soul, 1977 May 22; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Also pictured; Hoppy Hopkins.
    - Pee Wee Crayton & His Ultimates of Soul, 1976-1977, inclusive; B&W 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Taken at Roy's Rib Inn in Compton, Sloan's Lounge, 3860 Slausen Ave., Los Angeles. Also pictured; Charles Brown, Bill Clark, Leon Goss, Mr. Sloane, Evans Walker, Bill Walker, and Lola Vels.
      See also; Series 3: Subseries 3, Crayton, Pee Wee.
    - Phil Woods Quartet, 1988 October 5; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Protuberance, 1996,1998; Color and B&W snapshots (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured Paul Pulaski, Mark Weaver, and David Wayne.
    - Radius, 2001 April 30; B&W snapshots (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Also pictured; Alan Lechusza, Damon Smith, Dave Wayne, and Mark Weaver.
    - Ray Anderson Pocket Brass, 1999 Oct. 11 or 12; 3x5 Color Snapshots (Box 6, Folder 6)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Anderson, Ray
    - Ray Crawford Quartet, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Keith-organ, Dumas-drums, Harold Howard-trpt.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Crawford, Ray.
    - Ray Pizzi Quartet, 1980; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Taken at the Bonaventure Hotel in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured; Gary Denton, Dave Edelstein, Ray Pizzi and Frank Zottoli.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Pizzi, Ray
    - Ressurection Brass Band, 1982 August 9; B&W 11x14 and 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Taken at MacArthur Park in Los Angeels, Ca. Also pictured, Gideon Honore'.
      See Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - Robert Crowley Orchestra, 1981 January 27; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      See also; Series 3: Subseries 4, Crowley, Robert.
    - Robert Porter Quintet, 1981 February 14; B&W 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Taken in San Francisco, Ca. Also pictured, Augusta Lee Collins.
    - Ron Miles Quartet, 2004 April 5; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 28)
      Taken at the Outpost Performance Space in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Eric Gunnison, Kent McLagen, and Roy Royston.
    - San Francisco Blues Festival, 1977 August 14; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Also pictured; John Breckow, Schoolboy Cleve, Albert Collins, Richard Cousins, Robert Cray, Willy Joe Duncan, Johnny Fuller, Al Geddins, Johnny Heartsman, David Ii, Al King, Little Willie Littlefield, Tom McFarland, Tom Mazzolini, Dr. Wild Willie Moore, Louisiana Red, Marinelle Redus, Johnny Rhodes, Curtis Salgado, Phillip Walker, Johnny Waters.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Albert Collins
    - San Francisco Blues Festival, 1978 August 12 and 13; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Also pictured; Iverson Minter (aka Louisiana Red), Mark Naftalin, Lonesome Sundown (aka Cornelius Green), Dennis Walker, and Phillip Walker.
    - Sona Terra, 2000 May 15; Color snapshot (Box 11, Folder 2)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Mann, Herbie.
    - Sonship, 1981 November 12; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Horace Tapscott at the Lobero Theatre in Santa Barbara, Ca.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Tapscott, Horace.
    - Stefan Dill Trio, 2000 December 4; B&W snapshots (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Also pictured, Dave Nielsen and Dave Wayne.
      Also know as Mustafa Stefan Dill. See also Series, 3: Subseries 3, Dill, Stefan.
    - Steve Lacy Trio and Steve Lacy Quintet, 2000-2003, inclusive (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Taken in Albuquerque and Santa Fe, NM. Also pictured; Irene Aebi, JJ Avenal, John Betsh, and George Lewis.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Lacy, Steve.
    - Straight Up, 2000, 2004; Color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Arlen Asher, Bob Fox, Giacomo Gates, Michael Morreale, David Parlato and John Trentacosta
    - Sun Ra Arkestra, 1981, 1985; B&W 8x10, 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 20)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Ra.
    - Supersax, 1980; B&W 11x14 and 8x10 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Note by Sayles/Morgan Associates Public Relations dated 1980 October 17 and attached to photograph reads, "Supersax -- nine-piece fast-fingering jazz ensemble, led by alto saxophonist Med Flory. With two Grammy nominations and one Grammy Award behind them, Supersax also has five LP's and countless guest appearances to their credit. Shown here in a Donte's appearance are: (l. to r.) Jay Migliori, tenor saxophone; Don Menza, tenor; Med Flory, alto; Lanny Morgan, alto; Jack Nimitz, baritone and Conte Candoli, trumpet. Fred Atwood is on bass and not seen is Lou Levy, piano. Note: Current permanent membership is ray Reed, tenor instead of Menza and new bassist is Monty Budwig."
      See also series 3: Subseries 3, Candoli, Levy, Menza. Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - The Blasters, 1981 Sept. 11; B&W 8x10, some tinted blue 8x10s (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Taken at the Whiskey-A-Go-Go in Los Angeles, Ca.
      See also Box 6: Folder 24
    - The Blasters, 1981 Sept. 11; 5x7 B&W (Box 6, Folder 24)
      See also Box 6: Folder 23
    - The Mighty Flyers, 1983 December 10; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Taken at Carlos O'Brian's in LaVerne, Ca. Also pictured; Honey Alexander, Rod Piazza, Bill Stuve, Bill Schwartz, and Jr. Watson. Steve Kilman sitting in.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Piazza, Rod.
    - Tom Guralnick Trio, 1995 November 4; B&W 8x10 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Taken in Albuquerque, New Mexico
      Publicity photograph. See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Guralnick, Tom.
    - United Front, 1981 February 15; B&W 8x10 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Taken in San Francisco. Carleton Hoffman - drums, Lewis Jordan - alto sax, Mark Izu - bass, George Sams - trumpet.
    - Vinny Golia Large Ensemble, 1982 March 14; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      Taken at University of California Los Angeles (UCLA).
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Carter, John and Golia, Vinny.
    - Bradford, Bobby, 1983-June-16 (Box 5)
- Research files, Series 4.
  - Papers, Subseries 2.
    Correspondence, programs, fliers, notes, transcripts of interviews and other papers arranged alphabetically by artist's last name.
    - 1979 S.F. Blues Fest (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A-F (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bradford, Bobby (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bradford, Bobby Interview 1976-9-17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bradford, Bobby Interview 1993-7-18&19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Carroll, Baikida E.J. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Carter, Betty (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Carter, John (Box 1, Folder 10)
      See Also; Oliver Lake, Bradford, Crouch, James Newton, Vinny Golia
    - Cline, Alex & Nels (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Crawford, H. Ray (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - El Monte Art Ensemble & Neiderlinger, Buell (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Farris, Rev. Lonnie (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Goldsmith, George (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Griffen, Curtis (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Gruntfest, John (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Hemphill, Julius (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Howard, Harold (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Janofsky, Bonnie (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Katz, Fred (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Kuntz, Henry & Kaiser, Henry (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Land, Howard & Blue Mitchell (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Levy, Lou (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Marsh, Warne (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Murray, David (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Newton, James (Box 2, Folder 13)
      See also; Lowe, Bradford
    - N-T (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Pepper, Art (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Piazza, Rod (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ressurection Brass Band (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Rhodes, Sonny (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Roach, Max (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - S.F. Blues Fest (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - S.F. Blues Fest 1978 Aug. 12 & 13 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      See Living Blues #41 on 1978 S.F. Blues Fest
    - Sams, George & Jordan, Lewis & St. James, Andre Lewis Jordan - Bells 21 (Box 3, Folder 2A)
      1 of 2 folders
    - Sams, George & Jordan, Lewis & St. James, Andre Lewis Jordan - Bells 21 (Box 3, Folder 2B)
      2 of 2 folders
    - Shakey Jake (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Shew, Bobby (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Supersax (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Tapscott, Horace: P.A.P.A. (Box 3, Folder 9A)
      1 of 3 folders
    - Tapscott, Horace: P.A.P.A. (Box 3, Folder 9B)
      2 of 3 folders
    - Tapscott, Horace: P.A.P.A. (Box 3, Folder 9C)
      3 of 3
    - The Blasters (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Turner, Johnny: Zavan - Blues with Feeling (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Vinson, Eddie "Cleanhead" (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Miss. Smokey (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Wright, Lamar (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Related Material, Series 6.
  - Links to websites, Subseries 1.
    Weber's poetry in Edward Fields Papers in University of Delaware http://www.lib.udel.edu/ud/spec/findaids/field/field04.htm University of Toronto, Canada, Laidlaw Library http://www.library.utoronto.ca/canpoetry/ucl_poetry3.htm#W
    - Index of Jazz Artists, last updated 2005; URL link (Folder 1)
      Search Gallery 41 site for an audio interview of many of the artists listed in this collections including Bobby Bradford, John Carter, Charlie Haden, Alex and Nels Cline, Vinny Golia and Art Pepper.
      http://www.gallery41.com/JazzArtists/